

AN NGUYEN THANH

Front End Developer

- Movember 19th,2001
- Male
- 0932795437
- fxannguyen201@gmail.com
- Mo Chi Minh City, Vietnam
- S CV Online: https://nguyen thanhan201.github.io/An-s-C V/

SKILLS

SCSS vs CSS



.



WordPress



Javascript

• • • • • • • • • • •

React JS

• • • • • • • • •

Github

OBJECTIVES

_ Short term(in the next year): Have a college degree and become a designer website for the company, accumulate more experience for work, work effectively and quickly. I Especially can use English like American through and through.

_Long term(in the next 2-3 years): The practical work experience that I have accumulated will be the basis for me to achieve my goal of becoming a senior designer website in the future, bringing success to my company, and creating a lot of trust for the company.

WORK EXPERIENCE

NOVEMBER 2021 - DECEMBER 2021

DESIGN WEB ECOMMERCE | Leader

Using: HTML5, CSS, JS, REACTJS, GITHUB, TRELLO

OCTOBER 2021 - NOVEMBER 2021

DESIGN WEB WORDPRESS | Leader

Using: HTML5, CSS, WORDPRESS, PLUGINS

JULY 2021 - SEPTEMBER 2021

FRONTEND DEVELOPER INTERN | Member

Using: HTML, CSS, JS, GITHUB, TRELLO

EDUCATION

2019 - 2022

STUDYING AT THU DUC COLLEGE OF TECHNOLOGY | Major: Information Technology

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- _ In my free time, i will learn some new effect and practice my english.
- _ Can connect people together. Have responsible for the work and my life. Always want to learn everyone to improve myself.

CERTIFICATIONS

2020

HAVE TOEIC CERTIFICATE WITH SCORE 450

2019

HAVE INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY CERTIFICATE 1, 2,3,4